Wake up in the mornin'
早上起床半醒
And I pull the covers over my head
不愿上学我把被子一掖
Hey-oh
Week is starting, week is starting
周一告警 周一告警
I gotta get it movin'
起床一切得赶紧
But I'd rather stay here instead
但我更想在家做停歇
Hey, hey
School is calling, school is calling
学校呼名 学校呼名
My hair's a disaster, don't know what to do
头发一团乱麻 没时间在乎
But I need to move faster to make it through
得抓紧赶快就这样上路
This crazy morning has got me confused
麻烦的早晨令我不舒服
Clock is racing, time is wasting
钟表不停 时间无影
Mind's in circles, brain is spacing
九到六点 大脑设定
Everywhere that I go
不管往哪里走
Everything that I do
不管什么事务
I can't shake these Monday blues
周一忧郁无法去除
'Cause some days, I can't find a way
有时倒霉 我迷失方位
Out of this haze, hope I'll be okay
路找不对 希望有安慰
Just can't seem to get it right
一切都像状况外
A cloud is hanging over me
乌云缭绕在我心底
Hey
Rain is falling, rain is falling
雨下不停 雨下不停
I wish it was the weekend
只希望周末还在
'Cause you know that's where I'd rather be
所有人希望呆在家里
Hey, hey
Friday's calling, Friday's calling
周五降临 周五降临
I wonder what things won't go my way
有什么事情使我不遭罪
Or if I'll ever make it through the day
我能否挺过周一这一回
I hope this feeling won't lead me astray
希望它们不要让我心累
You'll get through it, you can do it
终会过去 相信自己
With your gals, there's nothing to it
朋友一起 都没问题
Everywhere that I go
不管往哪里走
Everything that I do
不管什么事务
I can't shake these Monday blues
周一忧郁无法去除
'Cause some days, I can't find a way
有时倒霉 我迷失方位
Out of this haze, hope I'll be okay
路找不对 希望有安慰
Just when I feel like it might come crashing down
就在我感觉要崩溃和跌倒
turn my mood around!
I can count on my friends to help me
朋友总能扭转乾坤，成为我的依靠
With my gals, there's nothing to it!
朋友一起 都没问题
Everywhere that I go
不管往哪里走
With everything that I do
不管什么事务
I'll say goodbye to the Monday blues
周一阴郁被我们去除
'Cause I've got my friends with me
因为我和朋友一起
And the sunshine is all I see
让阳光照进我心底
Everywhere that I go
不管往哪里走
With everything that I do
不管什么事务
The world feels so fresh and new
世界满是全新之处
'Cause I've got my friends with me
因为我和朋友一起
And those blues are ancient history!
忧郁都是历史的遗迹！